Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Group 1, Series III: Affiliations
  - CLMP-Correspondence. Jan.-June, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CLMP-Correspondence. July-Dec., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - CLMP-Correspondence. 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - New School MFA Advisory Board, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - New School MFA Advisory Board-Meetings., undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New School MFA Advisory Board-Events and Catalogues., undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - PEN-Silverberg's PEN Application and letters of reference from M. Mark, William S. Burroughs, and Jaime Manrique. 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PEN-Correspondence. 1992-95, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PEN-Correspondence-Gay and Lesbian Committee. 1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PEN-Correspondence-Gay and Lesbian Committee. 1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PEN-Correspondence. 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PEN-Correspondence. Jan.-Apr., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PEN-Correspondence. May-Aug., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PEN-Correspondence. Sept.-Dec., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PEN-Correspondence Jan.-May, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PEN-Correspondence. Jun.-July, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PEN-Correspondence. Aug.-Dec., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PEN-Correspondence. 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PEN-Correspondence. 2000, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PEN-Email Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PEN-Chute, Marchette. PEN American Center: A History of the First Fifty Years., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PEN-Correspondence re: Membership., undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PEN-Correspondence re: Membership., undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PEN-Correspondence-Translation Committee., undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Group 1, Series IV: Business/Administrative Files
  - Subseries A: General Business/Administration Files
    - Activity Reports, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Apogeo-Correspondence re: Modern Primatives, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Articles-"Barney Rosset: The Art of Publishing II" Paris Review, Winter 1997-98., 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Articles re: Bertelsmann Purchase of Bantam Doubleday., undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Articles re: Favorite Poem Project., undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Articles-"High Risk, High Return." Manhattan File. Jan-95, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Articles re: Publishing Business., undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - City Lights, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Companies Act 1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Conference Packets, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Conjunctions Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Contracts-Samples and Models, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Copyright Guide, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence-General Business, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence-General Business [no date], undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Curbstone Press, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Donadio & Ashworth, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The English Agency (Japan) Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Events 1990-97, 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Events 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Events [no date], undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Events-Poets House, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Events-Silverberg as Panelist, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Grove Press Catalogue, 1949-82, 1949-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Congratulatory Letters re: Grove Acceptance, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Correspondence 1989, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Correspondence 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Correspondence 1998-99, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Office Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Press Releases, Office Memos, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Silverberg Severance Package, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Silverberg Terms of Employment, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Grove/Atlantic-Grove Titles, Sales, Author, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Insurance, Receipts, Misc. Financial, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Japan Uni Agency, Inc., undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Jerusalem International Book Fair, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Juno Publications, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - The Kitchen, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Mailing Lists/Addresses, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Marsh & Sheil Limited, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Mary Clemmey Literary Agency, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mercury Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Notebooks 1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Notebooks 1996 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Notebooks 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Notebooks 1997 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Notebooks 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Office Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Paris Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Peake Associates-General Correspondence 1992-94, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Peake Associates-General Correspondence 1995-98, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Peake Associates-Submissions, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Peake Associates-Titles and Clients, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Publishers' Catalogues, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Re/Search Publishing-Catalogue, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Re/Search Publishing-Correspondence 1984-90, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Re/Search Publishing-Correspondence 1991-97, 1991-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Re/Search Publishing-Correspondence re: Apogeo and Shake, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Rights Guide, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Roof Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Artspace, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Contract and Correspondence with NYU re: Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archive, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Book Jackets, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Book Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Book Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Catalogues, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Certificate of Incorporation, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Silverberg's Contract with Serpent's Tail, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correpondence 1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence 1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence 1994-96, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence with Pete Ayrton 1991-95, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence with Pete Ayrton 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence re: Closing of High Risk Books, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence to Contacts in the U.K., undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Correspondence re: Copelco Capital Inc. Case, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Email Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Financial Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-High Risk: An Anthology of Forbidden Writings, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-High Risk 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Job Descriptions, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Office Notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Photo of Amy Scholder and Ira Silverberg, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Serpent's Tail/High Risk-Tear Sheets, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Shake, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Professional Publishing Course Catalogue 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Tax Files, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Travel-Expenses, Airline Correspondence, Hotels, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Travel-Itineraries, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Whiting Foundation Report 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Group 1, Series V: Personal Files
  - Articles-"Reading(s) is Fundamental: Getting Writers to Out Week '90." by Ira Silverberg, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Articles-"Howling for the Masses?" by Ira Silverberg in Outweek 1/14/90, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Articles-"Book 'em Homo." by Ira Silverberg in Outweek 7/4/90, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Articles-"Is the Boom Going Bust?" by Ira Silverberg in The Advocate 11/6/90, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Articles-"Silverberg Moves to Grove/Atlantic as Editor-in-Chief." Publishers Weekly 11/25/96, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Articles-"Ira Silverberg Wrote the Book on How to Succeed in Publishing." Paper Feb-97, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Articles-"Silverberg Leaves Grove for Agency." Publishers Weekly 8/24/98, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Articles-Ira Silverberg Mentions, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bios, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Cooking Class Notebook, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (personal), 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (personal) [no date], undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Highschool Commencement Program, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Personal Finances, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Personal Finances-Lease and Real Estate Information, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Personal Items (misc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Photographs of Silverberg, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Resume, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Group 1, Series VI: Computer Files
  - Acker, Kathy CD, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Acquisitions List, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Billy Book I-David Ohle, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Billy Book II-David Ohle, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - CIGNA Healthcare of New York, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Client List 1990-96, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Client Lsit at Donadio & Olson, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Coe, Jonathan, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Elizabeth Bogner Recommendation, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Elizabeth Schambelan-Panelist Bios, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Frankfurt Copy-W. S. Burroughs, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Grants and Awards Directory-PEN, undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Invoice-Consultation on National Poetry Month, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Ira Silverberg Bio for PEN, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Ira Silverberg Bio, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Ira Silverberg-1099s, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Itinerary, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Jackie Susann Introduction, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Jessica Lustig Recommendation, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Kathy Acker Tribute, undated (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Word Virus Contract, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Bobbie O'Steen, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Lucas, Christopher-Guggenheim Fellowship, undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - The Nation, undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - National Poetry Month Invoice, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Pesce, Mark-The Playful World, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Resume, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Scammell, Michael, undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Silverberg Misc., undated (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - William S. Burroughs-Ginsberg Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - William S. Burroughs-Ginsberg Statement, undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - William S. Burroughs-Projects, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Yablonsky, Linda-Guggenheim Fellowship, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Ira Silverberg-Business Check Registry 12/2/1997-7/5/1999, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - In Mail, undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Out Mail, undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Misc. Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Disk I, undated (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Disk II, undated (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Disk III, undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Disk IV, undated (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Disk V, undated (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Disk VI, undated (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Disk VII, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Disk VIII, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Disk IX, undated (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Disk X, undated (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Disk XI, undated (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - SyQuest Disk I, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SyQuest Disk II, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SyQuest Disk III, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SyQuest Disk IV, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SyQuest Disk V, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SyQuest Disk VI, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Group 1, Series VII: Other Media
  - Acker, Kathy and Robert Gletry Project Reading, April 26, 1995; cuid38915 (Box 12, Audiocassette 7)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 88 minutes
  - Compact Disk-Acker, Kathy. Pussy, King of the Pirates. 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Compact Disk-Voys. Number 4, featuring Richard Grossman, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "A Different Light", September 29, 1997; cuid38916 (Box 12, Vhs 10)
    Duration: 42 minutes
  - Video-The Great APLseed Giveaway (Academy of American Poets) 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Acker, Kathy - Memorial, undated; cuid38917 (Box 12, Vhs 12)
    Duration: 126 minutes
- Group 1, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
  - American Book Jam. vol. 1, Spring, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - American Book Review. vol. 17, no. 4 April-May, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - American Poet Summer, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - American Poet Fall, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Art in America Jan., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bomb. no. 62 Winter, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Directory of Literary Magazines, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Spring/Summer, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Winter, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Spring/Summer, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Fall, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Winter, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Grove/Atlantic Catalogue Winter, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - I.D. vol. 45, no. 3 May, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Jazz, Jennifer. Bronx Brazil (a foreign movie) 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - A Literary Companion: 1991 Engagement Calendar 1991 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - National Book Awards Brochure, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New Museum News Winter, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Newsbreaks. vol. 13, no. 5 May, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Newsweek 12/22/97, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - New York Blade News. vol. 3, no. 5 1/29/99, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Obscenity Divinity. vol. 2, no. 1 1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Off the Wall Spring, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Poetry Project Newsletter. issue 166 10/11/97, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Poetry Project Newsletter. issue 168 2/3/98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Poets House Benefit Brochure 6/22/98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Publishers Weekly. vol. 245, no. 1 1/5/98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Publishers Weekly. vol. 245, no. 39 9/28/98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Publishing Trends. vol. 3, no. 11 Nov. 1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Publishing Trends. vol. 5, no. 7 July, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Publishing Trends. vol. 5, no. 8 Aug-98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Publishing Trends. Vol. 7, no. 8 Aug-00, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Roam 2/3/98, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Small Press Distribution Winter, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Sotheby's Catalogue-"Allen Ginsberg and Friends", undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Speer, Laurel. Under a Scorpion Sun., undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Step 4: A New Fourth Step Guide, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Subtext. vol. 2, no. 23 11/20/96, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Susann, Jacqueline. Once Is Not Enough., undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Updike, John. Die ZwSchrecken der Weihnacht., undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Wij, Koningin, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Wojnarowicz, David and James Romberger. Seven Miles a Second, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Wolford, Catalogue Spring/Summer, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Group 1, Series IX: Burroughs
  - Burroughs Projects-Compact Disk-Selections from the Best of William Burroughs 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Burroughs Projects-The Best of William Burroughs (CD box set)-Reviews and Publicity, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Burroughs Projects-The Best of William Burroughs (CD box set)-Correspondence with John Giorno, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Burroughs Projects-Ghost of a Chance-Posters and Press Release, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Book Cover, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Correspondence and Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Manuscript Draft, Notes, and Correspondence 7/24/97, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Manuscript Draft 10/9/97, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Manuscript Draft 10/9/97, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Manuscript Draft-Appendix 4/11/99, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Manuscript Draft-Grauerholz Introduction 9/24/99, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Manuscript Final Draft [no date], undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words-Publicity and Reviews, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Burroughs Projects-Publishing Agreement with Grove/Atlantic 6/17/97, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Burroughs Projects-Last Words of Hassan Sabbah. (transcribed from tape experiment) c.1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Burroughs Projects-Naked Lunch-Correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Burroughs Projects-Naked Luch-Movie Production Schedule, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Burroughs Projects-Naked Lunch: The Definitive Text. Proposal by Graurholz 2/20/99, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Burroughs Projects-Naked Lunch-25th Anniversary Publicity, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Burroughs Projects-Naked Lunch-Skerl, Jennie. "Introduction to the 25th Anniversary Edition of Naked Lunch.", undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Burroughs Projects-The Place of Dead Roads-Book Jacket and Press Release, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Burroughs Projects-Queer-Maya Vision (British Television) Adaptation Proposal, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Burroughs Project-Queer-Screenplay by David Ohle, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Burroughs Projects-The Third Mind-Agreement Acknowledging Cancellation of Publication 6/10/99, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Book Jacket, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 2/15/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 2/20/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 2/26/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 4/6/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 4/19/98 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 5/10/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 5/15/98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 5/24/98, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Mechanicals Draft 6/24/98, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Mechanicals Draft 6/26/98, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 8/11/99, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 8/18/99, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Grauerholz Draft 8/31/99, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Drafts and Outlines, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Editor's Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Burroughs Projects-Introduction by Ann Douglas, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Permissions and Agreements, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Publicity and Reviews, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Burroughs Projects-Word Virus-Silverberg's Note Pad, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Burroughs, William S. Jr. Speed and Kentucky Ham, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Brookner, Howard. Borroughs (a film), undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Caveney, Graham. The Priest, They Called Him., undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Caveney, Graham. The Priest, They Called Him.-Publicity and Reviews, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Douglas, Ann. Writings on Beats, 1995-97., 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Ellis, Simone. William Burroughs Interview., undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Grauerholz, James. Burroughs and Dharma (lecture at Naropa Institute). 6/24/99, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Grauerholz, James. Burroughs and Dharma (abridged). 5/6/00, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Grauerholz, James. Burroughs Speech., undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Grauerholz, James. Space Pilgrim: William S. Burroughs, a Personal Life (proposal)., undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Meyer, Stewart. "Shots from the Bunker." Pop Smear Magazine. 5/6/98, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Nealon, Jeffrey T. Junk and the Other: Burroughs and Levinas on Drugs., undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Ohle, David. Billy's Boxes., undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Ports of Entry: William S. Burroughs and the Arts., undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Quinn, Patrick. Prakriti Junction., undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Swales, Peter J. Burroughs in the Bewilderness. 1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Burroughs-Related Manuscripts-Wood, Brent. Bring the Noise! William S. Burroughs and Music in the Expanded Field., undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Burroughs/Silverberg-Christmas Cards and Thank You Letters, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-re: Ginsberg/Kerouac/Burroughs Estates, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz re: Burroughs Projects, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Matta re: Gysin CD release on CRASH, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz re: OSU Donation, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Grauerholz/Silverberg, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)